Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Jae-geol. anyone?
There is no one. sir.
Go deeper. will you?
I really saw someone.
Okay.
Come on.
Is someone there?
GWANGLIM
Good evening!
I'm Kim Da-Kyung.
I called you before.
Thank you. sir.
It's really hot.
So. you're a YouTuber?
A YouTube content creator. to be precise.
Here.
HORROR QUEEN DA-KYUNG
"Horror Queen."
I'm warning you!
If you have a weak heart.
you must leave at once!
I'm Da-Kyung. the Horror Queen.
I guess you wouldn't know.
So. what did you want to see me about?
I heard some rumors
that strange things are
happening at this station.
Is that true?
I'm sorry. May I ask you to leave?
Pardon?
People like you came by often.
Those who profit from other people's pain.
I have nothing to say to those people.
If it's about money...
Did I say I wanted money?
Please leave.
I brought a gift just in case...
How many times do I have to tell you?
Could that be
silkworm spirit?
Yes.
That is Korea's finest spirit. first
produced in Jeolla and Hwanghae
during the Joseon Kingdom era.
How do you have this?
My grandfather is a brewer in Jeonju.
Will you tell me about the rumors?
Even so. I can't.
That's too bad.
How about...
just one story?
This story begins with a young man.
Attention. please.
We've made an emergency
stop due to an issue at the station.
Hello?
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Please wait safely until
the issue is resolved.
Our train will depart shortly.
A Raison French Black. please.
You there!
Don't touch if you're not buying!
No. this is Yogo. I want French Black.
Where's French Black?
Excuse me.
Not there. over there.
Yes. that one.
You're so bad at this.
-Which college do you go to?
-What?
This is Black. that's Yogo.
and both are the same brand.
Then logically. you should
be searching the same shelf.
but you're looking at the wrong spot.
That'll be 9.500 won.
Okay.
You gave me the wrong one.
GANGNAM PREMIUM COLLEGE REMEDIAL CLASS
I gave you the wrong one.
What an asshole. staring at me like that.
She's too dumb to get a real job.
Gosh. what a moron.
The next stop is Yongdam Station.
The doors are on your right.
Holy shit.
What a moron.
Gosh. she's such a dumbass.
Hello?
-What is it?
-Have you had dinner. Son?
Did you drink?
Mom. I'm watching a lecture. I have to go.
Your class said you haven't
attended in two months.
-I got to go.
-I was worried.
Mom?
Mom.
What?
YOUNG WOMAN COMMITS
SUICIDE AT GWANGLIM STATION
The next stop is Gwanglim Station.
The doors are on your right.
You can transfer to line five for
Bangwoo. Hanam Seoksan. and Machon.
The platform gates are closing.
The train to Sinseok has just departed.
The next train will pass this station.
This train will not stop at this station.
Please take a step back
and wait for the next train.
DANGER. DO NOT ENTER
That incident
was ruled a suicide.
That was intriguing.
You got your story. so please leave.
Is it okay if I come...
Don't ever come back.
ANOTHER SUICIDE AT GWANGLIM.
ALREADY THE 6TH INCIDENT
-Da-Kyung.
-What?
-Did I startle you?
-No. it's nothing.
Without your glasses.
your eyes look so pretty.
So. how was it?
I love it.
I knew that story would work out.
Right. that story.
That rail suicide a few years
ago at Gwanglim Station...
Rail suicide?
Jeez. that's so drab.
She's got a good feeling about this one.
Oh. really?
But I wonder if the view count will go up.
Your last story was drab too.
and you lost what few subscribers you had.
Beauty and horror are
completely different.
Plenty of people like drab stuff.
Right.
Your last video was
watched maybe 100 times?
Lina. don't you have a shoot?
That's right.
She doesn't even know anything.
What the heck does she know?
The last one was really great.
but is there anything stronger?
I checked out your channel.
The videos on it had
fewer than a hundred views.
It used to be 100.000.
Then why the sudden drop?
Well. you know...
Beauty YouTubers took over.
I see.
And horror content has run out.
You've done enough.
Why do you keep pushing yourself?
Because I'm...
I'm...
Da-Kyung. the Horror Queen.
Maybe I should change this.
There was a student.
She endured a lot of pain
to obtain something she didn't have.
BUT... WHAT ABOUT THE NOSE?
What the heck just happened?
Attention. please.
We've made an emergency
stop due to an issue at the station.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Please wait safely until
the issue is resolved.
Our train will depart shortly.
It must be an accident.
Did someone jump again?
Mi-ju.
Sir!
It's been a long time. How have you been?
The next stop is Sindam Station.
How's your studying going?
You look so grown-up now.
Have you lost weight?
You look even more handsome too.
Stop it.
Sir. did you move?
I went to the café you recommended...
The doors are opening.
-Honey!
-Ji-in!
Why are you standing?
Aren't you going to sit?
The doors are closing.
The train will soon depart.
-The doors are closing.
-Who is she?
She looks so adorable.
She's the student I used to tutor.
Your tutee?
Say hi. This is my girlfriend.
I'm getting off next.
-Sure. okay.
-It was good meeting...
I think she had her double eyelids done.
Don't say that.
What should we eat?
-What should we eat?
-What do you feel like?
The platform gates are closing.
GWANGLIM
Your nose is so pretty.
Thank you.
All officers are currently
busy taking reports.
You'll be connected to an officer shortly.
This is 911.
I'm at a subway station.
There's a crazy person
chasing me with acid.
Someone's chasing you with acid?
I've hidden in the bathroom.
Please tell me your exact location.
Gwanglim Station.
The women's room at Gwanglim Station?
Yes. please come quickly!
Try to stay calm. Could
you describe this woman?
Her face is bandaged.
She's in a hospital gown.
Hello?
How did you know it was a woman?
Your nose is so pretty.
Your face is so pretty.
You don't seem to believe me.
No. it's not that.
Where did you hear this story. sir?
My goodness. I'm getting tipsy.
7.3 million daily subway passengers
spend 35.1 minutes in
subways per day on average.
And Gwanglim records the highest
number of disappearances nationwide.
I am here at Gwanglim Station.
Did you see that? It
must be a poltergeist.
It has to be a poltergeist!
Okay. continue!
Now?
Okay. I...
I'll be...
telling you a mysterious
true story linked to this station.
I'm warning you!
If you have a weak heart.
you must leave at once!
I'm Da-Kyung. the Horror Queen.
How is it?
Da-Kyung.
Yes?
The horror queen is back.
The subject matter is
fun. and the pace is quick.
It's quite good.
Thank... Thank you.
Huh? What's this?
What do you...
What's what?
Did you see that?
What is that?
Isn't that a person?
This is a ghost. right?
Was this ever captured before?
Would you like a drink?
I actually quit drinking.
I heard your views went
up. We should celebrate.
One more glass. please.
What do you think a subway is?
Public transportation.
Usually. yes.
But for some people. it's life itself.
That man's beginning wasn't bad.
He was an ordinary man
like any other office worker.
But little by little. he
started to lose what he had.
He lost a decent job.
and then lost his family.
then. self-restraint.
He kept spiraling downwards.
And he finally reached the cold bottom.
Sir!
Wake up!
Come on. wake up.
You can't sleep here.
Oh. dear.
You know very well that
people walk around here.
Please move to that side.
BIG CUP SPICY NOODLE 2.500 WON
You there!
Don't touch if you're not buying!
Every damn day...
Here.
No. this is Yogo. I want French Black.
What are you doing here?
Did you move to this spot?
Don't cower. man.
Give me everything in your pockets.
Now. asshole.
Is this everything?
Shit.
I'll see you soon.
Let's be friends.
Son of a bitch.
I'm going to rip that fucking
bastard up into pieces.
You son of a bitch!
Do I look like a chump.
you fucking asshole?!
Fuck.
Damn it.
That fucking son of a bitch.
SOJU
Mr. Kim?
Is that you?
What's with your clothes?
Gosh. look at you.
What are you doing?
Shouldn't we share all the good stuff?
It'd be rude of you to keep
it for yourself. You'd look...
What? What's going on?
What is this?
You bastard!
No!
Save me!
Help!
Please save me!
4.400 won. please.
Sir. your change.
Goddamn.
No!
Come on...
Help!
Since then. clothes without owners
have been found at the station.
So...
is this the kind of story
you wanted to hear?
I'll take them all down...
Those who look down on me...
I'll never go easy on them.
Congratulations.
For what?
Surpassing 300.000 views.
Thank you.
But...
I didn't just want to
congratulate you for that.
To be honest...
I like you. Da-Kyung.
This one.
And this one would
suit you perfectly. Lina.
-Really?
-Yes.
Just pick one outfit for me. okay?
I think this one is better.
You think so?
LINA 5.9M DA-KYUNG 670K
I mean. she doesn't
even do her own makeup.
How can she shamelessly
call herself a beauty YouTuber?
Even if it's supposed to be fun.
she should at least have a
bare minimum of integrity.
How is she any different from those
girls who dance for donations every day?
I was talking about someone I can't stand.
They say when you hate
someone for no reason.
it's because you see yourself in them.
Who says nonsense like that?
If it's not true. just say it.
There's no need to yell at me.
I'm sorry.
I got too angry.
What do you dislike so much about her?
The way she gains popularity through lies.
Is that really the reason?
I think this one might be better.
This one should do.
Okay.
Thank you.
I don't even know.
People always...
desire what they don't have.
They could be happy just
seeing what they already possess.
Trying to obtain what you lack...
can lead to losing everything.
I'm no different.
I don't have much time left now.
So...
maybe it's time for you to
stop coming here as well.
Huh?
What's going on?
One million views in the shortest time!
Congrats. Da-Kyung!
-One million!
Congrats on one million views. Da-Kyung.
-Congratulations!
-I knew it.
Thank you!
-Congrats!
-Great job!
EVERYONE. THIS IS ALL TRUE!
NEVER GO THERE! I
EXPERIENCED IT FIRSTHAND!
Enjoy your coffee.
Da... Da-Kyung.
EVERYONE. THIS IS ALL TRUE!
Is this...
I see.
You need to take down all your videos.
Why?
This story shouldn't
be known to the world.
What do you mean by that?
I had an incident at the
convenience store there.
What...
The Church of Gwanglim...
The Church of Gwanglim?
Wait.
Isn't that the cult that
disappeared decades ago?
That's right.
The station was built on
top of the church chapel.
That's why strange things
keep happening there.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
Da-Kyung!
You mustn't go there!
If you go there. you'll all die!
What are you doing? Let go of my hands!
You must take down all the videos!
CHURCH OF GWANGLIM MASS SUICIDE
THAT DAY 50 YEARS AGO
GWANGLIM MASS SUICIDE
50 YEARS AGO ON OCTOBER 3. 1973
40 GWANGLIM FOLLOWERS COMMITTED
MASS SUICIDE AT THE CHAPEL IN SEOUL
HORROR QUEEN DA-KYUNG
You need to take down all your videos.
Why?
This story shouldn't
be known to the world.
DELETE CHANNEL
You've achieved your goal now.
If you stay the course. you
can easily get what you want.
So why not stop now?
Hold on.
-The views were so high this time.
-It was a good story.
Da-Kyung.
-I'll head out first.
-I'll talk to you later.
Is something wrong? You
didn't even say hi this morning.
Do you have something to say?
If you're free tonight. why
don't we have dinner together?
The takoyaki place I
mentioned should still be open.
I was actually going to
take you out last night.
but I was working out of the office.
You were in the office last night.
What?
I was out all day with Producer Kim.
So. would you be free tonight?
Yes. I'm free tonight.
But I'd rather just focus on work
than eat with someone like you.
You need more stories?
Yes.
If possible...
something definitive.
Sorry to say. but I have
no more stories to tell.
Nothing?
My health has gotten much worse.
Even the hospital says
I should stop working.
Just one more then.
One last story.
Please?
Haven't a million people
already liked the stories?
I want more...
even more people to like them.
You've already achieved what you wanted.
What more do you need?
Fucking damn it.
I've come this far. and
now you want to quit?
That's not fair!
You're not going to live
much longer anyway.
There was someone like you.
She lived for the attention
of others. just like you.
The circumstances were different. though.
But guys.
you know I don't just
recommend anything. right?
I got a tip for a makeup
look that will last a full day.
I'm sharing it only
because I genuinely liked it.
Of course. it's an ad.
The next stop is Gangnam Terminal Station.
-My babies. I'm here.
-The doors are on your right.
That's it for today. Bye!
Seriously!
The doors are closing.
This is so annoying!
I knew that story would work out.
Rail suicide?
Jeez. that's so drab.
She's got a good feeling about this one.
Oh. really?
Don't be so hard on Da-Kyung.
Huh? About what?
What are you saying?
That's how we stimulate each other.
You know she's the only
one who gets stimulated.
Woo-jin. you talk so strangely.
It sounds like I check on her.
So. when should I help with the filming?
No need to help. Just come eat with me.
Lina.
Your nose is bleeding.
Shit. how embarrassing.
Have you touched anything
dirty with your hands recently?
No. I don't think...
Shit!
I remember now.
I touched some weird phlegm on the subway.
Phlegm?
Doctor.
This isn't a bacterial
infection or anything. is it?
I'll prescribe some medicine.
Let's monitor it for a while.
This is so nasty.
And here. Could you sign this. please?
Of course.
How did you recognize me?
Pardon?
I know it's rare to see the
number one beauty YouTuber.
It's not that. This is a consent form.
Please sign here.
This is so embarrassing.
Da-Kyung.
What brings you here?
I'm following up on a story.
Right. that drab story.
Are you...
using that as an excuse to snoop on me?
What?
I'm kidding.
I hope you do well.
So you can get a good contract.
Sure.
Do you have something to say?
No. not really.
You're bleeding...
Lina. we're starting.
-One million!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Congrats!
-Horror Queen all the way!
-You're on fire!
Cheer for her!
-Let's reach ten million next!
-Let's go!
-Congrats!
-Let's go for ten million!
I'm Lina.
The number one beauty YouTuber.
Choi Lina of Lina's World.
The next stop is Gwanglim Station.
The doors are on your right.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Lina?
Do you need help?
I'm okay. Just go.
Are you really okay?
Piss off. please!
Oh no.
You've heard about the
Church of Gwanglim. right?
I've heard everything.
I heard this station was
built on top of its chapel.
and that's why strange
things keep happening here.
40 GWANGLIM FOLLOWERS COMMIT MASS SUICIDE
They supposedly committed
suicide for their leader's immortality.
Some people even believe
that the leader is still alive here.
Is this true?
What if it really is?
I want to investigate this organization.
Would you like to meet him?
The person you've dialed is not available.
After the tone. please leave a message.
I'm free tonight.
But I'd rather just focus on work
than eat with someone like you.
Woo-jin.
They're looking for Da-Kyung.
May I help you?
I'm Detective Park Ju-ho from Mapo Police.
Do you know where she is?
May I ask what this is about?
We came here after
seeing her YouTube videos.
At 3:34 a.m. on Friday.
a train will arrive.
If you ride that train.
you'll be able to meet him.
The train for... is approaching.
Please board the train safely
after passengers have exited.
PRODUCER WOO-JIN
The train is now arriving.
The platform gates are opening.
Our train will depart shortly.
Excuse me!
Please!
For goodness' sake!
The station master
is a different person?
Yes. but in the video. she
stated that she interviewed him.
and the recording was uploaded.
but the current station
master is a different person.
So...
who has she been interviewing?
A man who went missing three years ago.
Hello?
I knew from the first moment I saw you
that your desire would
bring you to this place.
You were always curious
about these stories.
but you were never curious about me.
Who I am
and why I'm telling you these stories.
The last story I'll tell you
is my own.
What are you looking at so intently?
It's just that...
I think I saw someone over there.
-At this hour?
-Yes.
I'm sure someone went in there.
No way! I have to go to the dormitory.
Hey.
Will you stop feeding that damn cat?
That's a pig. not a cat.
He's Ming-Ming. Don't call him a pig.
Stop giving me crap.
What are you going to do if
someone really went in there?
You know how flustered I was
when all those YouTubers came down here
and made all that fuss about some cult.
I went that time too.
Exactly.
So you can go again.
It's always me!
Gosh. who would be in
the station at this hour?
Hello?
Anyone there?
Of course not.
Jae-geol. anyone?
There is no one. sir.
Go deeper. will you?
I really saw someone.
Okay.
Dang it.
Hey. Jae-geol!
Double back the way you came from.
Hello?
Buddy!
It's... so hot...
Hello?
Hey!
Why is it so hot in here?
Jae-geol!
Is that you. Jae-geol?
Damn...
Gosh...
What in the world...
What the...
No...
Come on!
Damn it.
What are these?
Shit...
It's hot...
So hot...
It's so hot...
Ouch. that's hot!
Come on!
EMERGENCY BOX
Station Master?
Gosh!
Hello? Jae-geol?
I'm over here.
Jae-geol. I'm trapped inside a train.
Where are you?
Sir.
I can see you.
Jae-geol. where are you?!
On my way...
I... see you.
Be ri... there... Station Master?
You can see me?
Hey!
My gosh.
No!
No! Please!
Open the door! Open up!
Open the damn door!
I'm sure you heard
that this station used
to be the cult's chapel.
I can let you meet him.
No.
Please open the door.
Open this door!
I quite enjoyed our time together.
I'll...
miss you.
No...
Open the door. please!
Open the door!
Sir.
Please! No!
No!
No.
The train to Sinseok has just departed.
Da-Kyung.
Why did you never answer
your phone? I was so worried...
Woo-jin.
Do you want me to tell
you an interesting story?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm